{
  "questions":
  [
    {
      "category": "Verbs",
      "question": "Have Sat",
      "answer": "Sein Gesessen"
    },
	{
      "category": "Verbs",
      "question": "Have Laid",
      "answer": "Sein Gelegen"
    },
	{
      "category": "Verbs",
      "question": "Have Stood",
      "answer": "Sein Gestanden"
    },
	{
      "category": "Vocabulary",
      "question": "January",
      "answer": "Jänner"
    },
	{
      "category": "Vocabulary",
      "question": "This Year",
      "answer": "Heuer"
    },
	{
      "category": "Vocabulary",
      "question": "Stairs",
      "answer": "Stiege"
    },
	{
      "category": "Vocabulary",
      "question": "Chimney",
      "answer": "Rauchfang"
    },
	{
      "category": "Vocabulary",
      "question": "Potatoes",
      "answer": "Erdäpfel"
    },
	{
      "category": "Vocabulary",
      "question": "Whipped Cream",
      "answer": "Schlagobers"
    },
	{
      "category": "Vocabulary",
      "question": "Ground Beef",
      "answer": "Faschiertes"
    },
	{
      "category": "Vocabulary",
      "question": "Green Beans",
      "answer": "Fisolen"
    },
	{
      "category": "Vocabulary",
      "question": "Cauliflower",
      "answer": "Karfiol"
    },
	{
      "category": "Vocabulary",
      "question": "Brussels Sprouts",
      "answer": "Kohlsprossen"
    },
	{
      "category": "Vocabulary",
      "question": "Apricots",
      "answer": "Marillen"
    },
	{
      "category": "Vocabulary",
      "question": "Tomatoes",
      "answer": "Paradeiser"
    },
	{
      "category": "Vocabulary",
      "question": "Pancakes",
      "answer": "Palatschinken"
    },
	{
      "category": "Vocabulary",
      "question": "Semi-sweet cottage cheese",
      "answer": "Topfen"
    },
	{
      "category": "Vocabulary",
      "question": "Horseradish",
      "answer": "Kren"
    },
		{
      "category": "Verbs",
      "question": "Have Driven",
      "answer": "Sein Gelenkt"
    }
  ]
}
